

# **Ming-Yang Ho**



ikaminyou@gmail.com

github.com/Kaminyou

in linkedin.com/in/kaminyou

+886 952792255

## Summary ·

A data scientist at aetherAI with 4+ years of experience in 2D/3D computer vision, natural language processing, machine learning, and deep learning algorithms development.

Besides, I am also adept at web programming, cryptography, and clinical pharmacy.

## Skills -

- Programming related
  - · Python
  - ·Cython
  - · ReactJS
  - · C/C++
  - $\cdot$ MySQL
  - · Web security
  - Docker
  - ·Linux
  - ·Git
- Others
  - ·Adobe Ps/Ai/Id/Pr/Lr
  - Psychiatry
  - ·Clinical pharmacy

# Language ·

- · Mandarin (native)
- ·English (TOEIC 825) [2014]
- · Japanese (JEPT N2) [2018]

#### **Interests**

#### Machine learning, Deep learning, Full stack development, Cyber security

### Work experience

#### **Data Scientist**

aetherAI, Oct. 2021 - (Current)

#### **Teaching Assistance (TA)**

NTU EE Machine Learning, Feb. 2021 - Jul. 2021

NTU EE Web Programming, Feb. 2021 - Jun. 2021

NTU CSIE Bioinformatics and Cheminformatics, Sep. 2020 - Jan. 2021

#### Data Engineer (ML) Intern

Dcard, Jun. 2020 - Dec. 2020

- · Built an automatic image cropping system to attract users' attention.
- · Invented a malicious applicants detection system with SimCLR.
- · Established a system to immediately detect offensive comments.

#### **Deep Learning Researcher Intern**

Institute of Information Science, Academa Sinica, Jul. 2019 - Aug. 2019

· Leveraged the concept of RGB channels to assist in SNP prediction.

### Honors

#### 2021 PyCon APAC Speaker

Get 3D models out of nothing: Python implementation of deep learning-based 3D models reconstruction from 2D images..

#### 2021 PyCon TW Speaker

Implementation of a deep learning-based saliency detection system by Python

#### 2020 HITCON Speaker

Potential Security and Privacy Issues in Novel Taiwanese National eID system

#### **Awards**

#### 2021 Outstanding Paper Award

**Multi-label Classification on CT Medical Imaging Competition, 3rd prize** ICH detection enhanced by asymmetric loss with CNN-LSTM approach.

### **Recent Projects**

### 2021 SUPERB: Speech processing Universal PERformance Benchmark

Entrusted by NTU, CMU, MIT, and Facebook AI to build a leaderboard web server for SUPERB Benchmark. (https://superbbenchmark.org/)

# 2021 Template is all you need: 2D to 3D reconstruction with template learned by contrastive learning

Developed a 2D to 3D reconstruction DL model leveraging the template concept.

### Education

#### 2019~2021 Master of Science (@CSIE CMDM) GPA 4.20

Computer Science (bioinformatics specialization) *BEBI, National Taiwan University (NTU)* 

#### Thosis

Look, Listen, and Diagnose: a deep learning based comprehensive Parkinson's disease evaluation system with 3D point cloud and acoustic features

#### 2014~2019 Doctor of Pharmacy GPA 4.06

Clinical Pharmacy

School of Pharmacy, National Cheng Kung University (NCKU)

### **Publications**

Liu, L. C., Ho, M. Y., Su, B. H., Wang, S. Y., Hsu, M. T., & Tseng, Y. J. (2021). PanGPCR: predictions for multiple targets, repurposing and side effects. *Bioinformatics*, 37(8), 1184-1186.

**Ho, M. Y.**, Kuo, M. C., et al. (2021) A step toward practical digital markers for monitoring patients with Parkinson's disease using a deep-learning-based AI-assisted 3D camera system for gait assessment. *Clinical Parkinsonism & Related Disorders*. [under review]

**Ho, M. Y.**, Kuo, M. C., et al. (2021) Look, Listen, and Diagnose: a deep learning based comprehensive Parkinson's disease evaluation system with 3D point cloud and acoustic features. [unpublished manuscript]

**Ho, M. Y.**, Kuo, M. C., et al. (2021) A 2D camera is all you need: gait analysis with frontal-view 2D video by deep learning-based 3D estimation. [unpublished manuscript]